motorsportauctions.com 2017-03-15

# Extra Page 11 Title

**Motorsport Auctions Ltd Privacy Notice**

## 1\. Introduction

Your personal information is being processed by the Motorsport Auctions Ltd. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal information. We comply with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998 and aim to maintain consistently high levels of best practice in our processing of your personal information. This Privacy Notice relates to our use of any personal information you provide to us through **motorsportauctions.com**

In order to provide you with the full range of services, we may request and/or record information about you. This privacy notice explains the following: 

  * the type of information we collect;
  * how the information is used;
  * when we may contact you;
  * whether we will disclose your details to anyone else; and
  * the use of cookies.

The **motorsportauctions.com** website contains hyperlinks to websites owned and operated by third parties. These third party websites have their own privacy notices and we encourage you to review them. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for the privacy practices of such third party websites and your use of such websites is at your own risk. 

## 2\. Personal information collected

When you sign up to participate in or receive a service from **motorsportauctions.com** website, such as buying, bidding or selling through our website, we will ask for limited personal information. We will also collect personal information from you when you communicate with us over the telephone or via written correspondence. This can include information such as your name, postal address, telephone or mobile number, fax number, email address, gender or date of birth. By entering your details in the fields requested, you enable Motorsport Auctions Ltd and its service providers to provide you with the services you select. 

“We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties” 

## 3\. How will the information be used?

Motorsport Auctions Ltd will use your personal information for a number of non-marketing purposes including the following: 

  1. we may contact you for service related reasons that you have subscribed to, signed up for, or participate in. 
  2. to invite you to share your opinions and comments through a research study about the level of service you receive from us; 
  3. to track traffic flows and to make our website easier for you to use; 
  4. to provide a user online community; 
  5. planning and managing our business activities by understanding aggregated analysis on behaviour and habits; 
  6. as we may be required to by law; 
  7. to assist with problem solving in order to improve our services; 
  8. to resolve disputes between buyers and sellers. 

## 4\. Marketing contact policy

Yes. Motorsport Auctions Ltd may use the information you have provided to promote the products and services of Motorsport Auctions Ltd or others. 

However, be assured that we understand the irritations of unsolicited communications and are fully committed to ensuring the rights and obligations set out in the Data Protection Act 1998 and the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003 are respected. 

**If you don't want it, you won't get it**. Any marketing communication you receive will always include a clear, simple option to refuse, or 'opt-out' of such future communications. You may also opt-out at ANY time by contacting us (see below). 

The Telephone Preference Service (TPS) and the Mailing Preference Service (MPS) offer consumers important statutory and non-statutory protection against unsolicited marketing contact. If you are registered on either service, Motorsport Auctions Ltd will assume that your _subsequent_ submission of personal data via our website or data capture form indicates, for the time being, your consent to receive marketing by us. **You may opt-out at ANY time by contacting us (see below).**

## 5\. Will my information be shared?

We may disclose your personal data where we believe we are compelled to do so by law; in particular for the prevention or detection of crime, the capture or prosecution of offenders; and the assessment or collection of tax or duty. 

Occasionally, we may share your contact information with carefully selected third party companies whose products and services we feel may be of interest to you. We will keep these offers relevant to your interests. It's easy to unsubscribe from any email or mobile messages you no longer want. (see below). 

We use a number of third party organisations to help provide a professional service to our customers (i.e. fulfillment bureaus, call centers’, website designers and payment agencies). These organizations act as data processors and are strictly controlled in how they may/may not use your personal data. We remain responsible for the protection of your data. 

Please note that some of our partners may be located outside the European Economic Area (EEA). Countries outside the EEA may not be required to protect personal information as stringently as countries inside. 

## 6\. Can I see information held on me?

Under the Data Protection Act 1998 you have the right to request a copy of the personal information that Motorsport Auctions Ltd holds about you. There will be an administration fee of £10 associated with this request and will require two pieces of identification to prove your identity. Please make a written application to the Data Protection Officer, Motorsport Auctions Ltd, 35 Galileo Gardens, Cheltenham, GL51 0GA, UK 

If any of the personal information that we hold about you is incorrect, you can click on the contact us link on the website. 

## 7\. Changes to this privacy policy

This privacy policy may be updated at any time with or without notice in order to comply with new practices or regulations. You may wish to visit this page every time you submit personal information to our website. 

## 8\. Cookies and your privacy

In order to enable us to provide you with a personalised browsing experience, this website uses 'cookie' information collection technology. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are issued to your computer when you enter a website. Cookies are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive, and they can be used for a wide range of purposes, such as identifying your computer's previous visits to a website, and to ascertain the most popular features of a website. 

This website uses cookies as they enable us to identify your computer when you visit the website. For example, cookies can make it possible for us to identify and automatically log in registered users of certain services on the website without the need for us to ask users for their registration details and password each time they visit. We also use cookies to develop a clearer picture of which parts of the website are the most popular to its visitors, and your preferences. Cookies are also used in behavioural advertising to identify users who share a particular interest so that they can be served more relevant adverts.

If you wish to know more about cookies and how companies like us use them, please visit [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/) or [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) Information on these websites will assist you in exercising your privacy rights providing guidance on how to opt-out of future access or continued storage of information via cookies. 

Following recent revisions of the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 relating to the notification and use of cookies we are currently working towards implementing the new requirements in line with guidance provided by The Information Commissioner's Office. 

## 9\. Company contact details

If you have any further questions or comments concerning your privacy, please contact; 

Data Protection Officer  
Motorsport Auctions Ltd  
35 Galileo Gardens  
Cheltenham  
GL51 0GA  
UK 

Copyright © 2017 Motorsport Auctions Ltd. All Rights Reserved.

Use of this Web site constitutes acceptance of our Terms and Conditions and our Privacy Policy.   
Designated trademarks and brands are the property of their respective owners.
